pornrapidshare.com 2010-05-22

# Privacy Policy

| 

**Commitment**

Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) is a social networking site where people can create their profiles, connect with new people, share their photos and videos, write blogs, use public and private forums . This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com)'s policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any Personal Information you submit to us through our Website.

Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) ("Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com)", "us" or "we") respects the privacy of the visitors to its Website.  
Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) may update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes by placing a prominent notice on this page and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  
If any change is unacceptable to you, you must cease using our Website. Continued use of our Website following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

**Information we collect**

You agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy.

The security of your personal information depends on your protection of your account password. Please do not disclose your account password to any other person. Please bear in mind though, that it is impossible for Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) to guarantee all necessary security measures. For example, we cannot control any illegal and/or unforeseen activity of other users that may allow them to get around the privacy or security settings on the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) website. Consequently, you acknowledge that there are circumstances in which your personal information may be accessed by unauthorized persons.

We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our Website:  
When you start registration process to have access to the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) Services as a Member, we will collect your name and e-mail address. We will collect any other information, including but not limited to your age, your hobbies and interests and other content, such as photos, music and videos, when you enter this information in your profile.

When you enter Personal Information throughout the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) network using one of the features of the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) network, for example journals, testimonials, groups, or message boards, lifestyle choices, groups with whom you are affiliated (schools, companies), private messages, bulletins or personal statements (collectively "Profile Information"), we will collect any such information you enter. Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) recommends that you exercise discretion in deciding what information you disclose on the Internet.

When you contact us by sending us an e-mail, we will collect your e-mail addresses and any information contained in the e-mail you send us.

Once you register with Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. If you are browsing the Website without registering with Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com), you are anonymous to us, but we will collect the information with all available technologies. Whether you are Member or Visitor of the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) Website, we receive and store information which is transmitted automatically from your computer when you browse the Internet and use Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com). This information includes information from cookies, your IP address and browser type (which are described in section below).

If you become aware of any breach of data security or have any other questions about the security of our website, please contact us: [info@pornrapidshare.com](mailto:info@pornrapidshare.com)

**Cookies and information collected via technologies**

Certain information may also be automatically collected and stored on our server logs, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, and operating system. We also use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed, or on which of the advertisements displayed on the Website you clicked. This type of information is collected to make our services and solutions more useful to you and to tailor the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) community experience to meet your special interests and needs.  
If you search the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) community by using a toolbar that Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com), or a third party provides, we may collect Anonymous Information about you automatically, but we will not collect Personal Information.

An "Internet protocol address" or "IP Address" is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We track your IP Address when you login to the Website.

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that a web site sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a web site. Cookies are a common Internet technology and most Internet browsers (such as Internet Explorer and Safari) are initially set up to accept cookies. Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Website. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Website may not work properly.  
Other third parties may place advertisements and cookies on web pages within the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) network. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.  
Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) may link information stored in cookies such as your age, gender and country with your personally identifiable information and we may use such information to gather statistics about the number of people who visit Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) and to customize Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com)'s content, layout and services for delivery to you.

Our advertising partners may set and access cookies or use other technologies such as web beacons (which are electronic files that allow a web site to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies) in order to personalize advertising content. Use by these advertising partners of their own cookies and any other tracking technologies are subject to their privacy policies.

**Use of Information**

We will display your personal information on your profile according to the preferences you set. We will use your name so that you are recognizable on our database and so that we can personalize your experience. We will use your email address to contact you from time to time and may also use it for security reasons to confirm that you are who you say you are.

You can control what part of your profile information and photos is visible to visitors of the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) Website.  
In order to provide useful information about social networks to people who might be interested in joining the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com), we may use your profile information and photos on the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) website and when we send emails, for example when we send birthday reminders to Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) members or when we send general newsletters to members of Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com). When you decide to view a member's profile, we may show that Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) member that you choose to view their profile. If you don't want us to show to other Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) members that you viewed their profile, you can change this in your privacy settings.

The Personal Information that Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) members enter into the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) profile will be used for the search feature to search for other members by different criteria, like location or gender.  
Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) may analyze any collected information for its own internal purposes, for instance we may use the information collected automatically, such as your IP address and information stored via cookies, to gather statistics about the number of people who visit Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) and to customize Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com)'s content, layout and services. We also may share this information with third parties to help us improve Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) and better serve our users.

We limit access to personal information about you to employees and third parties who we reasonably believe need access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.  
However, no company, including Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com), can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

Advertisements that appear on Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) are delivered to you by our advertising partners. Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) may transfer information about your use of Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com), such as your IP address and information stored via cookies, to our advertising partners and other third parties. This information may be used to provide advertising, promotions and other products and services that may be of particular interest to you. It may also be used to provide you with a tailored choice of content and media products. If you do not want to receive targeted advertisements at any point in the future, please change your advertisement preferences in your account or send a request to us via the Contact Us page.

Our advertising and promotions partners have no access to your name or personal contact information stored by Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) unless you choose to share it with them. Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) does not provide your name or personal contact information to an advertising partner when you interact with or view a targeted advertisement.

We may provide your personally identifiable information and the data generated by cookies and the aggregate information to the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us in providing our services to you. Such third party entities will be obligated to use your personally identifiable information solely to provide the services to us.

We will disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or to protect the rights and property of Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com).com, its affiliates or the public. We may also co-operate with law enforcement agencies in any official investigation and we may disclose your personally identifiable information to the relevant agency or authority in doing so.

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com).com, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. If an acquiring company should plan to materially change this privacy policy, we will notify you beforehand.

**Sharing of the information**

Except as explained herein, or where you are expressly informed otherwise, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information unless required by law or for the protection of your Membership. However, Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) may share profile information and aggregate usage information in a non-personally identifiable manner with advertisers and other third parties in order to present to Members and other users of the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) website more targeted advertising, products and services; provided that, in such situations, we will never disclose information that would personally identify you. As set forth above, Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) may (i) use your email address to conduct market research for Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com)'s internal use only; and/or (ii) use your email address to market Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) to you (e.g., new features and applications, announcements, opportunities of interest). Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) may contract with a third party to conduct such research and marketing; provided that such third party will be fully bound by an obligation of confidentiality to Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) and may not use any personally-identifiable information provided by Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) other than as expressly instructed by Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) and in strict compliance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Children under 13**

Children under the age of 13 are not eligible to use Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) and must not attempt to register with Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) and/or submit any personal information to us. Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) does not knowingly collect personal information from any person who is under the age of 13 or allows them to register. If it comes to our attention that we have collected personal data from a person under the age of 13, we will delete this information as quickly as possible. If you have reason to believe that this has occurred, please contact us via the Contact Us page, and we will delete any such information.

**Links**

Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) Website provides links to other website or location That is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents. **We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these outside websites or their content.** Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy does not apply to these outside websites and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Web site and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information.

In certain circumstances, Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) may use "Masking" (programming techniques such that the displayed URL does not match the actual pages being viewed) and, although it will appear that you are still on the Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) Web site, you may be on a different site. For example, when you create a widget or when you upload a video, you may be transferred to a third party's site and the privacy policy of the applicable third party site applies.

**Changing and removing information**

You always have the option to review, delete, correct and revise your privacy settings and personal profile, including who has access to your personal profile in your account at any time or contact us for assistance via the Contact Us page. Requests of this nature will be completed within 48 hours.

**Tell-a-Friend**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com), we will ask you for your friends name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com). Pornizer.com (Pornrapidshare.com) stores and only uses this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may submit a request that we remove this information from our database via the Contact Us page or by emailing; remove requests of this nature will be completed within 30 days.  
Contact information

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](mailto:info@pornrapidshare.com).

Free Porn Ad

Who is online (648)

|
